 questions = [
    {
        "question": "How was the early atmosphere formed?",
        "correctAnswer": "Volcanoes releasing lots of gas",
        "answer0": "Plants photosynthesise to produce Oxygen",
        "answer1": "Animals respire and produce Carbon Dioxide",
        "answer2": "Oceans produced lots of gas",
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the early atmosphere mostly made of?",
        "correctAnswer": "Carbon Dioxide",
        "answer0": "Oxygen",
        "answer1": "Ammonia",
        "answer2": "Nitrogen",
    },
    {
        "question": "What was not produced from volcanic activity?",
        "correctAnswer": "Oxygen",
        "answer0": "Water Vapour",
        "answer1": "Nitrogen",
        "answer2": "Methane",
    },
    {
        "question": "How were the oceans formed?",
        "correctAnswer": "Water Vapour in the atmosphere condensed",
        "answer0": "Volcanoes produced liquid water",
        "answer1": "Carbon Dioxide condensed",
        "answer2": "Oxygen reacted with Carbon Dioxide",
    },
    {
        "question": "How was lots Carbon Dioxide removed from the early atmosphere?",
        "correctAnswer": "Dissolved in the oceans",
        "answer0": "Condensed and formed oceans",
        "answer1": "It wasn't removed",
        "answer2": "Plants photosynthesise",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is our atmosphere mostly made of?",
        "correctAnswer": "Nitrogen",
        "answer0": "Oxygen",
        "answer1": "Water Vapour",
        "answer2": "Carbon Dioxide",
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of radiation comes from the sun and isn't absorbed by greenhouse gases?",
        "correctAnswer": "Short wavelength",
        "answer0": "Thermal radiation",
        "answer1": "Long wavelength",
        "answer2": "Infrared radiation",
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of radiation is reflected off the Earth and absorbed by greenhouse gases",
        "correctAnswer": "Long wavelength",
        "answer0": "Short wavelength",
        "answer1": "Infrared radiation",
        "answer2": "Gamma radiation",
    },
    {
        "question": "What form of human activity does not affect the amount of greenhouse gases in the atmosphere?",
        "correctAnswer": "Breathing",
        "answer0": "Burning fossil fuels",
        "answer1": "Agriculture",
        "answer2": "Deforestation",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is not a consequence of climate change?",
        "correctAnswer": "Nicer weather",
        "answer0": "More natural disasters",
        "answer1": "Reduction in biodiversity",
        "answer2": "Rise in sea levels",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a Carbon Footprint?",
        "correctAnswer": "A measure of the mount of Carbon Dioxide is released over  full cycle of something",
        "answer0": "How much Carbon is released per step",
        "answer1": "A footprint in the ground made of Carbon",
        "answer2": "The amount of Carbon released by smoking",
    }
]
